Guide to the Muawia Barazangi papers, 1969-2015..
Barazangi, Muawia papers,
- Series VI. Miscellaneous documents
  - Curriculum Vitae for Muawia Barazangi, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Series VII. Department Files
  - EAS chair search committee, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Nominating committee for endowed professorships, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Visits and meeting notes, 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Ahwaz Iran visit, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Legalizing websites correspondence and documents, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Taofik Mourabit visit, 1997-10 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Engineering staff seminar, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Centers Directors, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Engineering Policy Committee and other matters, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Department/field affairs, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Center directors/research staff promotions, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Oliver Celebration, 1993-08 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Guiliana Mele visit, Italy, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Giuliana Italy paper, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Ralph Alewine visit, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Department of Geological Sciences and INSTOC annual report, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Department of Geological Sciences and INSTOC annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Indirect cost correspondence, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Alimam visit, 1994-10 (Box 6, Folder 16)